<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Decklist Deck="BloodBraidElf-Jund">
  <DesignGoal>Optimized Jund Cascade Midrange - Modern Legal</DesignGoal>

  <!-- 1-Drops (8) -->
  <Card>
    <Name>Birds of Paradise</Name>
    <Quantity>4</Quantity>
    <Type>Creature — Bird</Type>
    <Cost>{G}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Flying
{T}: Add one mana of any color.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Ragavan, Nimble Pilferer</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Legendary Creature — Monkey Pirate</Type>
    <Cost>{R}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Whenever Ragavan, Nimble Pilferer deals combat damage to a player, create a Treasure token and exile the top card of that player's library. Until end of turn, you may cast that card.
Dash {1}{R}</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Fatal Push</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Instant</Type>
    <Cost>{B}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Destroy target creature if it has mana value 2 or less.
Revolt — Destroy that creature if it has mana value 4 or less instead if a permanent you controlled left the battlefield this turn.</RulesText>
  </Card>

  <!-- 2-Drops (11) -->
  <Card>
    <Name>Wrenn and Six</Name>
    <Quantity>3</Quantity>
    <Type>Legendary Planeswalker — Wrenn</Type>
    <Cost>{R}{G}</Cost>
    <RulesText>+1: Return up to one target land card from your graveyard to your hand.
−1: Wrenn and Six deals 1 damage to any target.
−7: You get an emblem with "Instant and sorcery cards in your graveyard have retrace."
Loyalty: 3</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Scavenging Ooze</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Creature — Ooze</Type>
    <Cost>{1}{G}</Cost>
    <RulesText>{G}: Exile target card from a graveyard. If it was a creature card, put a +1/+1 counter on Scavenging Ooze and you gain 1 life.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Tarmogoyf</Name>
    <Quantity>4</Quantity>
    <Type>Creature — Lhurgoyf</Type>
    <Cost>{1}{G}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Tarmogoyf's power is equal to the number of card types among cards in all graveyards and its toughness is equal to that number plus 1.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Terminate</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Instant</Type>
    <Cost>{B}{R}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Destroy target creature. It can't be regenerated.</RulesText>
  </Card>

  <!-- 3-Drops (10) -->
  <Card>
    <Name>Kitchen Finks</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Creature — Ouphe</Type>
    <Cost>{1}{G/W}{G/W}</Cost>
    <RulesText>When Kitchen Finks enters the battlefield, you gain 2 life.
Persist (When this creature dies, if it had no -1/-1 counters on it, return it to the battlefield under its owner's control with a -1/-1 counter on it.)</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Tireless Tracker</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Creature — Human Scout</Type>
    <Cost>{2}{G}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Whenever a land enters the battlefield under your control, investigate.
Whenever you sacrifice a Clue, put a +1/+1 counter on Tireless Tracker.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Klothys, God of Destiny</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Legendary Enchantment Creature — God</Type>
    <Cost>{1}{R}{G}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Indestructible
As long as your devotion to red and green is less than seven, Klothys isn't a creature.
At the beginning of your precombat main phase, exile target card from a graveyard. If it was a land card, add {R} or {G}. Otherwise, you gain 2 life and Klothys deals 2 damage to each opponent.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Kolaghan's Command</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Instant</Type>
    <Cost>{1}{B}{R}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Choose two —
• Return target creature card from your graveyard to your hand.
• Target player discards a card.
• Destroy target artifact.
• Kolaghan's Command deals 2 damage to any target.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Seasoned Pyromancer</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Creature — Human Shaman</Type>
    <Cost>{1}{R}{R}</Cost>
    <RulesText>When Seasoned Pyromancer enters the battlefield, discard two cards, then draw two cards. For each nonland card discarded this way, create a 1/1 red Elemental creature token.
{3}{R}{R}, Exile Seasoned Pyromancer from your graveyard: Create two 1/1 red Elemental creature tokens.</RulesText>
  </Card>

  <!-- 4-Drops (8) -->
  <Card>
    <Name>Bloodbraid Elf</Name>
    <Quantity>4</Quantity>
    <Type>Creature — Elf Berserker</Type>
    <Cost>{2}{R}{G}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Haste
Cascade (When you cast this spell, exile cards from the top of your library until you exile a nonland card that costs less. You may cast it without paying its mana cost. Put the exiled cards on the bottom of your library in a random order.)</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Huntmaster of the Fells</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Creature — Human Werewolf</Type>
    <Cost>{2}{R}{G}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Whenever this creature enters the battlefield or transforms into Huntmaster of the Fells, create a 2/2 green Wolf creature token and you gain 2 life.
At the beginning of each upkeep, if no spells were cast last turn, transform Huntmaster of the Fells.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Chandra, Torch of Defiance</Name>
    <Quantity>1</Quantity>
    <Type>Legendary Planeswalker — Chandra</Type>
    <Cost>{2}{R}{R}</Cost>
    <RulesText>+1: Exile the top card of your library. You may cast that card. If you don't, Chandra, Torch of Defiance deals 2 damage to each opponent.
+1: Add {R}{R}.
−3: Chandra, Torch of Defiance deals 4 damage to target creature.
−7: You get an emblem with "Whenever you cast a spell, this emblem deals 5 damage to any target."
Loyalty: 4</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Questing Beast</Name>
    <Quantity>1</Quantity>
    <Type>Legendary Creature — Beast</Type>
    <Cost>{2}{G}{G}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Vigilance, deathtouch, haste
Questing Beast can't be blocked by creatures with power 2 or less.
Combat damage that would be dealt by creatures you control can't be prevented.
Whenever Questing Beast deals combat damage to an opponent, it deals that much damage to target planeswalker that player controls.</RulesText>
  </Card>

  <!-- Removal & Disruption (8) -->
  <Card>
    <Name>Lightning Bolt</Name>
    <Quantity>4</Quantity>
    <Type>Instant</Type>
    <Cost>{R}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Lightning Bolt deals 3 damage to any target.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Thoughtseize</Name>
    <Quantity>3</Quantity>
    <Type>Sorcery</Type>
    <Cost>{B}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Target player reveals their hand. You choose a nonland card from it. That player discards that card. You lose 2 life.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Abrupt Decay</Name>
    <Quantity>1</Quantity>
    <Type>Instant</Type>
    <Cost>{B}{G}</Cost>
    <RulesText>This spell can't be countered.
Destroy target nonland permanent with mana value 3 or less.</RulesText>
  </Card>

  <!-- Lands (23) -->
  <Card>
    <Name>Verdant Catacombs</Name>
    <Quantity>4</Quantity>
    <Type>Land</Type>
    <Cost></Cost>
    <RulesText>{T}, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Verdant Catacombs: Search your library for a Swamp or Forest card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Wooded Foothills</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Land</Type>
    <Cost></Cost>
    <RulesText>{T}, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Wooded Foothills: Search your library for a Mountain or Forest card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Bloodstained Mire</Name>
    <Quantity>1</Quantity>
    <Type>Land</Type>
    <Cost></Cost>
    <RulesText>{T}, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Bloodstained Mire: Search your library for a Swamp or Mountain card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Overgrown Tomb</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Land — Swamp Forest</Type>
    <Cost></Cost>
    <RulesText>({T}: Add {B} or {G}.)
As Overgrown Tomb enters the battlefield, you may pay 2 life. If you don't, it enters the battlefield tapped.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Stomping Ground</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Land — Mountain Forest</Type>
    <Cost></Cost>
    <RulesText>({T}: Add {R} or {G}.)
As Stomping Ground enters the battlefield, you may pay 2 life. If you don't, it enters the battlefield tapped.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Blood Crypt</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Land — Swamp Mountain</Type>
    <Cost></Cost>
    <RulesText>({T}: Add {B} or {R}.)
As Blood Crypt enters the battlefield, you may pay 2 life. If you don't, it enters the battlefield tapped.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Blackcleave Cliffs</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Land</Type>
    <Cost></Cost>
    <RulesText>Blackcleave Cliffs enters the battlefield tapped unless you control two or fewer other lands.
{T}: Add {B} or {R}.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Nurturing Peatland</Name>
    <Quantity>1</Quantity>
    <Type>Land</Type>
    <Cost></Cost>
    <RulesText>{T}: Add {B} or {G}.
{1}, {T}, Sacrifice Nurturing Peatland: Draw a card.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Raging Ravine</Name>
    <Quantity>1</Quantity>
    <Type>Land</Type>
    <Cost></Cost>
    <RulesText>Raging Ravine enters the battlefield tapped.
{T}: Add {R} or {G}.
{2}{R}{G}: Until end of turn, Raging Ravine becomes a 3/3 red and green Elemental creature with "Whenever this creature attacks, put a +1/+1 counter on it." It's still a land.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Forest</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Basic Land — Forest</Type>
    <Cost></Cost>
    <RulesText>({T}: Add {G}.)</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Mountain</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Basic Land — Mountain</Type>
    <Cost></Cost>
    <RulesText>({T}: Add {R}.)</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Swamp</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Basic Land — Swamp</Type>
    <Cost></Cost>
    <RulesText>({T}: Add {B}.)</RulesText>
  </Card>
</Decklist>
