<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Decklist Deck="Dimir Inverter">
  <DesignGoal>a</DesignGoal>
  <Card>
    <Name>Inverter of Truth</Name>
    <Quantity>4</Quantity>
    <Type>Creature — Eldrazi</Type>
    <Cost>{2}{B}{B}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Devoid (This card has no color.)
Flying
When Inverter of Truth enters the battlefield, exile all cards from your library face down, then shuffle all cards from your graveyard into your library.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Thassa's Oracle</Name>
    <Quantity>4</Quantity>
    <Type>Creature — Merfolk Wizard</Type>
    <Cost>{U}{U}</Cost>
    <RulesText>When Thassa's Oracle enters the battlefield, look at the top X cards of your library, where X is your devotion to blue. Put up to one of them on top of your library and the rest on the bottom of your library in a random order. If X is greater than or equal to the number of cards in your library, you win the game. (Each {U} in the mana costs of permanents you control counts toward your devotion to blue.)</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Jace, Wielder of Mysteries</Name>
    <Quantity>3</Quantity>
    <Type>Legendary Planeswalker — Jace</Type>
    <Cost>{1}{U}{U}{U}</Cost>
    <RulesText>If you would draw a card while your library has no cards in it, you win the game instead.
+1: Target player mills two cards. Draw a card.
−8: Draw seven cards. Then if your library has no cards in it, you win the game.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Opt</Name>
    <Quantity>4</Quantity>
    <Type>Instant</Type>
    <Cost>{U}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Scry 1.
Draw a card.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Thoughtseize</Name>
    <Quantity>4</Quantity>
    <Type>Sorcery</Type>
    <Cost>{B}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Target player reveals their hand. You choose a nonland card from it. That player discards that card. You lose 2 life.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Dig Through Time</Name>
    <Quantity>4</Quantity>
    <Type>Instant</Type>
    <Cost>{6}{U}{U}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Delve (Each card you exile from your graveyard while casting this spell pays for {1}.)
Look at the top seven cards of your library. Put two of them into your hand and the rest on the bottom of your library in any order.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Fatal Push</Name>
    <Quantity>4</Quantity>
    <Type>Instant</Type>
    <Cost>{B}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Destroy target creature if it has mana value 2 or less.
Revolt — Destroy that creature if it has mana value 4 or less instead if a permanent you controlled left the battlefield this turn.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Censor</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Instant</Type>
    <Cost>{1}{U}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Counter target spell unless its controller pays {1}.
Cycling {U} ({U}, Discard this card: Draw a card.)</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Thought Erasure</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Sorcery</Type>
    <Cost>{U}{B}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Target opponent reveals their hand. You choose a nonland card from it. That player discards that card.
Surveil 1. (Look at the top card of your library. You may put it into your graveyard.)</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Drown in the Loch</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Instant</Type>
    <Cost>{U}{B}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Choose one —
• Counter target spell with mana value less than or equal to the number of cards in its controller's graveyard.
• Destroy target creature with mana value less than or equal to the number of cards in its controller's graveyard.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Omen of the Sea</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Enchantment</Type>
    <Cost>{1}{U}</Cost>
    <RulesText>Flash
When Omen of the Sea enters the battlefield, scry 2, then draw a card.
{2}{U}, Sacrifice Omen of the Sea: Scry 2.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Swamp</Name>
    <Quantity>3</Quantity>
    <Type>Basic Land — Swamp</Type>
    <Cost>
    </Cost>
    <RulesText>({T}: Add {B}.)</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Island</Name>
    <Quantity>6</Quantity>
    <Type>Basic Land — Island</Type>
    <Cost>
    </Cost>
    <RulesText>({T}: Add {U}.)</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Watery Grave</Name>
    <Quantity>4</Quantity>
    <Type>Land — Island Swamp</Type>
    <Cost>
    </Cost>
    <RulesText>({T}: Add {U} or {B}.)
As Watery Grave enters the battlefield, you may pay 2 life. If you don't, it enters the battlefield tapped.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Drowned Catacomb</Name>
    <Quantity>4</Quantity>
    <Type>Land</Type>
    <Cost>
    </Cost>
    <RulesText>Drowned Catacomb enters the battlefield tapped unless you control an Island or a Swamp.
{T}: Add {U} or {B}.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Choked Estuary</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Land</Type>
    <Cost>
    </Cost>
    <RulesText>As Choked Estuary enters the battlefield, you may reveal an Island or Swamp card from your hand. If you don't, Choked Estuary enters the battlefield tapped.
{T}: Add {U} or {B}.</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Fetid Pools</Name>
    <Quantity>2</Quantity>
    <Type>Land — Island Swamp</Type>
    <Cost>
    </Cost>
    <RulesText>({T}: Add {U} or {B}.)
Fetid Pools enters the battlefield tapped.
Cycling {2} ({2}, Discard this card: Draw a card.)</RulesText>
  </Card>
  <Card>
    <Name>Fabled Passage</Name>
    <Quantity>4</Quantity>
    <Type>Land</Type>
    <Cost>
    </Cost>
    <RulesText>{T}, Sacrifice Fabled Passage: Search your library for a basic land card, put it onto the battlefield tapped, then shuffle. Then if you control four or more lands, untap that land.</RulesText>
  </Card>
</Decklist>